team-dignitas.net 2019-09-08

# Privacy Policy - Pages - Dignitas

Team-Dignitas (“ **we** ”, “ **us** ”) is committed to safeguarding and respecting the privacy of all visitors and their personal data. This privacy policy explains and aims to provide the detailed information of what happens to the personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you, including the details of our steps towards its procession and protection. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

## **INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU**

We may collect and process the following data about you:

Information that you provide to us by filling in forms on our site www.team-dignitas.net (“ **Our Site** “). This includes information provided at the time of registering with Our Site and when requesting and/or supplying goods, services or information from/to us or third parties.

Information that you provide to us when you register for an account either on this website or in the Team Dignitas mobile App.

Information that you provide to us when you login to the Team Dignitas mobile App with a Facebook, Twitter, Twitch or other social account.

Information that you provide to us when you write to us (including email communication).

Information that you provide to us when we speak to you by telephone or in person. We may make and keep a record of the information you share with us.

Information that you provide to us by completing surveys or participating in competitions. We may ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you have no obligations to respond to them.

Details of transactions you carry out through Our Site or otherwise with us and of the fulfilment of your orders with third parties concluded through Our Site or otherwise.

Details of your visits to Our Site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

Website statistics in the purpose of supporting its optimisation, which might include your visited pages and the overall journey followed through Our Site. Such statistics may also include details of your browser and operating system used. We would like to mention that we are not able to identify individuals based on such information.

Information obtained by us from third parties in accordance with the Act.

## **HOW WE MAY USE THE COLLECTED INFORMATION**

We use information held about you in the following ways:

To ensure that content from Our Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.

To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.

To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.

To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.

To notify you about changes to our service or in relation to activities you have undertaken, such as entry into competitions and giveaways.

We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by post or telephone.

If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.

If you are a new customer, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data (the order form or registration form).

We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women in SW1). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers’ wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.

## **DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by post, email or telephone.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

If we or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by us about our customers will be one of the transferred assets.

If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions of Website Use and/or other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of us, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations, such as credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies, for the purposes of fraud protection and prevention, credit risk reduction and to pursue debtors.

If we use a third party to host the servers on which your personal information is stored.

In any other manner mentioned elsewhere in this policy.

## **HOW WE STORE, PROCESS AND SECURE YOUR INFORMATION**

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfillment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of Our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to Our Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## **TEAM DIGNITAS MOBILE APP**

The Team Dignitas mobile App is managed by a 3rd party called Heero Ltd. Heero collects the following data and uses it for the following purposes:

Heero collects your name, email address and User ID from the Social Network you choose to login with, should you choose to share it at the time of login. Heero will also capture Usage data against your User Account:

To understand general usage of the mobile App in order to provide updates and fixes.

To notify you in the event of a service update, or in relation to competitions and giveaways that you may have entered into via the mobile App.

To notify you in relation to any subscription service or product that you have purchased via the mobile App.

To record your preferences inside the mobile App.

Heero will not share your identifiable information with 3rd parties except in relation to form entries that you have submitted for competitions and giveaways that have been provided by a 3rd party.

## **SOCIAL MEDIA PLATFORMS**

Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that Our Site and it’s owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.

Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate / engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details. This website nor its owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email.

Our Site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on Our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on Our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## **SOCIAL MEDIA AND SHORTENED LINKS**

This website and it’s owners through their social media platform accounts may share web links to relevant web pages. By default some social media platforms shorten lengthy URLs [web addresses].

Users are advised to take caution and good judgement before clicking any shortened URLs published on social media platforms by our  site and it’s owners. Despite the best efforts to ensure only genuine URLs are published, many social media platforms are prone to spam and hacking and therefore this website and it’s owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any shortened links.

## **EXTERNAL LINKS**

Although this website only looks to include quality, safe and relevant external links users should always adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website.

The owners of this website cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite their best efforts. Users should therefore note they click on external links at their own risk and this website and it’s owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.

## **COOKIES**

The Team-Dignitas website uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies. Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device. Our site uses cookies dropped by us or third parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website. Also, cookies may also be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites.

## **ACCESS TO INFORMATION**

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

## **CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. However, we advise that you check this page regularly to keep up to date with any necessary changes.

## **FURTHER RESOURCES**

Please visit the following websites if you would like to find out more about areas surrounding the protection of your personal data.

Data Protection Act:  
<http://www.legislation.gov.uk/ukpga/1998/29/contents>

Data Protection Act – The Guide:  
[http://www.ico.org.uk/for_organisations/data_protection/the_guide](https://www.ico.org.uk/for_organisations/data_protection/the_guide)

Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003:  

Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003 – The Guide:  
[http://www.ico.org.uk/for_organisations/privacy_and_electronic_communications/the_guide  
](https://www.ico.org.uk/for_organisations/data_protection/the_guide)

Please find the privacy policies of the third party websites we use the most when sharing hyperlinks to external resources but please note the following list is not only limited to the listed websites.

Facebook privacy policy:  

Google privacy policy:  

LinkedIn privacy policy:  

Twitter privacy policy:
